Hi, I'm Annie with the face
and we're here at our exhibition with Damson Madder. Come join me
over here. We've got the food,
we got some beer. I'm gonna help myself.
Cheers!
Here we have the MUD larking space.
Hi!
Who doesn't love bird watching?
Let's go to Chickaganda.
I love to roller skate.
Tell me about your look. Tell me about the skirt.
So the skirt is damson matter?
Of course. I never usually wear long skirts,
but I absolutely love this one. It looks very cute.
Tell me about the look today.
So I went for stripes. Matching.
So cute. So cute,
so chic. You look so cute,
so chic. Thank you.
Alright guys, that's a wrap.
Thanks for joining us. Until next time.